Tomasz Brzoza

Phone: (+48) 53 53 33 292

E-mail: tombrzoza50@gmail.com

GitHub: github.com/tombrzo

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/tomasz-brzoza-245399175/

www: https://portfolio-35a24.firebaseapp.com/

For many years I used to work in the tourism industry organizing business trips and flights. I've worked with people for people.

Nowadays my main professional goal is to find a job that will give me an opportunity to deepen and improve my programming skills, engage in interesting and creative projects and raise my Front-End development qualifications.

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Git
- Customer needs identification
- Responding to customer concern

Projects

- Portfolio single page application based on React Router
- AppLab landing page based on JavaScript, SCSS
- Facebook Clone single page application based on React Router
- Places to go single page application based on React Router
- Weather App based on JavaScript, CSS
- Notify landing page based on HTML and CSS

Education

1988-10 1993-06

Adam Mickiewicz University in Poznań Institute of Anthropology and Ethnolog

Experience

2007-08 - 2020-09 Travel Consultant , Weco Travel Sp. z o.o., Rainbow Tours S.A., Poznań

• customer service

• preparing commercial offers

• making reservations and selling airline tickets

2006-01 - 2007-07 Travel Consultant, Exodus Travels Ltd., London

• making reservations and selling airline tickets

• customer service

1994-08 - 2005-12 Travel Consultant, Blue Sky Travel, Fantur s.c., Poznań

• making reservations and selling airline tickets

• customer service